Braidey Hooper

SKILLS

Highly upbeat and goal oriented. Excels in positions of leadership with nearly six years of customer service experience and six years of medical experience. Well versed in advanced health sciences and hospitality with a hunger to learn more.

EXPERIENCE

University of Kansas Saint Francis Emergency Department, Topeka Ks - Patient Care Tech

November 2022 - Current

- Responded quickly to medical emergencies.
- Multitasked the essential needs of up to 40+ patients.
- Worked closely with doctors, nurses, and other staff to save patient's lives.
- Trained incoming staff in a constantly changing environment.

Stormont Vail Hospital, 6 North Oncology and Med/Surg, Topeka Ks - Patient Care Tech

September 2021 - November 2022

- Became proficient in the charting system known as Epic.
- Understood plans of care and executed care tasks accordingly.
- Rapidly learned avenues of treatment for corresponding diagnoses.
- Performed bedside care in a professional manner under adverse circumstances.
- Met rigorous expectations under the stress of being severely understaffed.

Olive Garden, Topeka Ks - Lead Server

August 2019 - December 2019

- Maintained excellent time management in a high paced work environment.
- Focused on pertinent objectives with shift-specific goals.

Trails Cafe, Holton Ks − Server → Manager

August 2016 - January 2019

- Learned quintessential interpersonal customer service skills.
- Became familiar with E7 POS system software.
- Managed employees and operated the fast paced front of house duties.
- Coordinated catering and event management for large groups.

EDUCATION

EdX KU Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp. Completed March 2024 — Developer Certificate.

Holton High School, Holton Ks. Graduated 2019 - High School Diploma.

AWARDS

Earned admittance to Washburn University's Law school Early Acceptance Program (LEAP) at 18 years old.

Published work in the Teen Ink national magazine publisher.